Friends, in this video we are going to know whether there is a
loan on that vehicle just by the vehicle number
or not. If you also have any
type of vehicle and you had taken that vehicle
on loan but you have paid off that loan
and you want to know whether your
loan is over or not or you have
taken an old vehicle i.e. a second hand vehicle
and you want to know whether there is a
loan on that vehicle or not or it is without a loan, then
how to find out, then through this video
we are going to know the loan of the vehicle just by the vehicle number, whether there is a
loan on that vehicle
or not, so watch the video completely till the end
so that you people can also provide complete information sitting at home,
live
proof, I am going to show through this video,
if you all like the video then
like the video and subscribe to the channel,
so let us know the
complete process of finding out the loan of the vehicle just by the vehicle number, step by
step. Before that, you people should also open
any browser in your mobile phone, laptop or computer.
In this, you all have to
write M Parivahan.
As soon as you search by writing M Parivahan,
after searching, whatever you all get  The
first option that is visible,
you all have to click on this option.
As soon as you click on it,
after clicking, this official website will open.
Its direct link will
also be found in the description of the video. By clicking from there,
you will easily
reach this website and here you all will
get to see an option, Information
Services. You all have to click on this option.
After clicking,
you will get to see an option, Know
Your Work Details. You
all have to click on this option. As soon as you
click on this, after clicking,
you will get to see this Citizen Login option.
Here, first of all, you all have to
register. Below, you all will
get to see an option, Create Account.
You all have to click on this option.
As soon as you click on this,
after clicking, this page will open. Here, first of all, you all have to
fill in the mobile number, email
ID and this captcha which is visible,
fill it in this box and
click on the Generate OTP option below.
After this, you all have to do it here.  You have to fill the name,
below you have to create a password, that is, you have to
create a password, the password which you will
write above, you have to write the same confirm password below as well,
after this you have to
click on the save option below and as soon as you click on the save
option, here you will
see Citizen User is Win
CreatedDrawerNavigator, you have to fill it and the
captcha which will appear here below,
you have to
click on the next option below,
after this you have to fill the password which you have created
here, below you have to
click on the continue option and as soon as you
click on the continue option,
after clicking, an OTP will come again on your number, you have to
verify, that OTP has to be
filled in this box and as soon as you
fill the OTP, after filling it
you have to click on the verify option below
and as you verify,
after verifying, this page will open here, for whichever vehicle, that is, for
whichever vehicle you
want to know whether there is a loan on that vehicle or not, then for
that vehicle, that is,  The vehicle
number has to be filled here, after this the
captcha which is visible here, that is, the captcha which is
visible here, if you do not understand the captcha
then you
can change the captcha by clicking on the refresh option, that
captcha has to be filled in this box, below
you have to click on the vehicle search option,
after this this page will open, in this page
you will get to see all the complete details of your vehicle,
here you can
see the validity of fitness, you will get to
see the registration date, you will get
to see the date of fitness and here you will get to
see the name of the company from which you have got the insurance done, if
you want to know about the finance then you will
come at the bottom, now here you will get to see Miller
Finance i.e. whether there is a
loan on your vehicle or not, if you will
see the option of yes in front of finance then
know that the loan is still running on your vehicle i.e. there is a
loan, if you will
see no here then there is no
loan on your vehicle and if you want to know
from which company the loan is running then
you will get to see the name of that company here also  It will be visible
i.e. the name of the loan will be visible.
I hope that after watching this video,
you all would have also known the complete process of checking the finance i.e. loan just by the vehicle number.
If
you all liked the video and want to get more such
information videos sitting at home and be the first to
get them, then do not forget to subscribe to the channel and
open the all notification
and share the video as much as possible
so that this information reaches everyone.